{
    "subject": "resource/Lower_Guadiana_International_bridge",
    "predicate": "ontology/crosses",
    "object": "resource/Chanza_River",
    "human_readable": "The Lower Guadiana International bridge crosses the Chanza River.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9571788311004639,
            "question": "What river does the Lower Guadiana International bridge cross?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8833503127098083,
            "question": "Where is the Lower Guadiana International bridge located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8128147125244141,
            "question": "What type of international bridge is the Lower Guadiana International bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6984946131706238,
            "question": "Are there any other bridges crossing the Chanza River?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6968774795532227,
            "question": "Is the Lower Guadiana International bridge a road or railway bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6717191338539124,
            "question": "Does the Lower Guadiana International bridge connect two countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6332488059997559,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Lower Guadiana International bridge for transportation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5674009919166565,
            "question": "Are there any environmental concerns related to the Lower Guadiana International bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.537595272064209,
            "question": "How does the Lower Guadiana International bridge impact local communities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27094709873199463,
            "question": "What are some of the historical uses of the Chanza River?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Lower Guadiana International bridge crosses the Chanza River.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7128_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the Lower Guadiana International bridge impact local communities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7128_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any environmental concerns related to the Lower Guadiana International bridge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7128_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the Lower Guadiana International bridge for transportation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7128_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7128_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to various documents (e.g., file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7128/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7128/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt), the Lower Guadiana International Bridge does indeed cross the Chanza River."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports this statement. For example, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7128/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt mentions \"The river can be crossed by using the Lower Guadiana International bridge\" and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7128/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt states, \"Overview: The Lower Guadiana International Bridge (Spanish: Puente Internacional; Portuguese: Ponte Internacional) is a bridge that crosses the Chan\u00e7a River connecting southern Spain and Portugal.\" Both pieces of information confirm that the Lower Guadiana International bridge does indeed cross the Chanza River."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Chanza River forms part of the Portugal-Spain border, while the Lower Guadiana International Bridge crosses the lower Guadiana River, not the Chanza River.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states the bridge crosses the Chanza River, but information provided mentions the bridge connects Spain and Portugal.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It conflicts with the information provided that the Lower Guadiana International Bridge crosses the shore of Chan\u00e7a, less than a hundred meters from a Spanish dam and the river Guadiana, not directly over the Chanza River.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that the Lower Guadiana International Bridge crosses the Chan\u00e7a River, not the Chanza River.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}